Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series A. Subject Files F-J, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series A. Subject Files
  - Subject Files G
    - Glover, Danny (Box A-47, Folder 75)
    - Danny Glover (Box A-47, Folder 76)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Karl Crutchfield,
    - Danny Glover (Box A-47, Folder 77)
    - Glover, D. Donald (Box A-47, Folder 78)
    - Glover, Esther (Box A-47, Folder 79)
    - Glover, Isaac (Rev. & Mrs.) (Box A-47, Folder 80)
    - Glover, I. G. Bishop (Box A-47, Folder 81)
      Photographer if identified: Bunny Photo Studio, Pope Studio
    - Glover, Israel (Box A-47, Folder 82)
    - Glover, Izeil (Box A-47, Folder 83)
    - Glover, John D. (Box A-47, Folder 84)
      Typescript caption stapled to recto of print.
    - Glover, Junior (Box A-47, Folder 85)
    - Glover, Kenneth (Box A-47, Folder 86)
    - Glover, Louis Mrs. (Box A-47, Folder 87)
    - Glover, Mel (Box A-47, Folder 88)
    - Mother Glover (Box A-47, Folder 89)
    - Glover, Thelma (Box A-47, Folder 90)
      Photographer if identified: Beuford Smith
    - Glover, Toni (Box A-47, Folder 91)
    - Goady, Charles W. (Box A-47, Folder 92)
      Photographer if identified: E. M. Joseph Studios
    - Godett, Carroll Mrs. (Box A-47, Folder 93)
    - Godfrey, Henry (Box A-47, Folder 94)
    - Godfrey, Lynnie (Box A-47, Folder 95)
    - Godfrey, Lynnie (Box A-47, Folder 96)
    - Godfrey, Jr. Ollin (Box A-47, Folder 97)
    - Godley, Harriet (Box A-47, Folder 98)
    - Godson, Kojalis (Box A-47, Folder 99)
    - "Godspell" in Harlem (Box A-47, Folder 100)
      2 prints stuck together and stuck to folder.
    - Godwin, Harold C. (Box A-47, Folder 101)
      Photographer if identified: U.S. Navy
    - Godwin, Lamond (Box A-47, Folder 102)
    - Godwin, Mills E. Jr. Gov. (Box A-47, Folder 103)
    - Godwin, Paul (Box A-47, Folder 104)
      Photographer if identified: James W. B. Burke
    - Godwin, Vincent (Box A-47, Folder 105)
    - Goff, Edgar (Box A-47, Folder 106)
    - Goff, Sam (Box A-47, Folder 107)
      Photographer if identified: Popsie
    - Goggins, Anita (Box A-47, Folder 108)
      Photographer if identified: Delta Air Lines
    - Goggins, Douglass (Box A-47, Folder 109)
    - Goines, Donald (Box A-47, Folder 110)
    - Goines, T. R. (Box A-47, Folder 111)
    - Goins, Clyde Lee (Box A-47, Folder 112)
    - Goins, Jr. Martin H. (Box A-47, Folder 113)
      Photographer if identified: U.S. Agency for International Development
    - Goings, Russell (Box A-47, Folder 114)
      Photographer if identified: Tommy Weber, Harris Photo
    - Golar, Martin (Box A-47, Folder 115)
    - Golar, Simeon (Box A-47, Folder 116)
      Photographer if identified: NYCHA, Harris Photo, Hamilton Associates, P.G. Franklin, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise,
    - Golar, Simeon (Box A-47, Folder 117)
      1 print is of Mike Forchand.
      Photographer if identified: Fabian Bachrach, NYCHA, Alex Summers,
    - Golar, Simeon (Box A-47, Folder 118)
      Photographer if identified: Fabian Bachrach, Hakim, King Photographers, NYCHA, Harris Photo,
    - Golar, Simeon (Box OS-1, Folder 1)
    - Gold, Quincy (Box A-47, Folder 119)
    - Gold, Quincy (Box A-47, Folder 120)
    - Goldberg, Arthur (Box A-47, Folder 121)
    - Goldberg, Jack (Box A-47, Folder 122)
    - Goldberg, Whoopi (Box A-47, Folder 123)
    - Goldberg, Whoopi (Box A-47, Folder 124)
      Photographer if identified: Joan Marcus, Sidney Baldwin, Shane Harvey
    - Goldberg, Whoopi (Box A-47, Folder 125)
      Photographer if identified: Darius Anthony, Bruce McBroom, Tony Esparza, Scott Haddad, Bob Greene, Juanita M. Cole
    - Golden, Arthur E. (Box A-47, Folder 126)
    - Golden Boy (Box A-47, Folder 127)
      1 print has caption stapled to recto.
    - Golden Boy (Box A-47, Folder 128)
    - Golden, Charles (Bishop) (Box A-47, Folder 129)
      Photographer if identified: Boston University Photo Service, Bro David McAdams
    - Golden Gate Quartet (Box A-47, Folder 130)
    - Golden, Howard (Box A-47, Folder 131)
      One computer-printed image.
    - Golden, Howard (Box A-47, Folder 132)
      Also campaign literature. 2 prints have staples through edge.
      Photographer if identified: Neil De Angelis, Chuck Lewis, Kathryn Kirk, Pictorial Enterprise, James Barnett,
    - Golden, Howard (Box A-47, Folder 133)
      Photographer if identified: Kathryn Kirk
    - Golden, Howard (Box A-47, Folder 134)
    - Howard Golden (Box A-47, Folder 135)
    - Howard Golden (Box A-47, Folder 136)
    - Golden State Mutual Life Insurance Co. (Box A-47, Folder 137)
    - Golden Ten (Box A-47, Folder 138)
    - Golden, Thelma Ann (Box A-47, Folder 139)
      Also 2 velox prints. 1 Polaroid print. One print has staple through edge.
    - Golden, Thelma O. (Box A-47, Folder 140)
    - Goldin, Harrison J. (Box A-47, Folder 141)
      4 pairs of prints are stuck together. 1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso. 1 print stuck to folder.
      Photographer if identified: Miriam Fishman, Pictorial Enterprise,
    - Goldman, Moe (Box A-47, Folder 142)
    - Goldsberry, Ronald E. (Box A-47, Folder 143)
    - Goldsborough, Bill (Box A-47, Folder 144)
    - Goldsby, Richard (Dr.) (Box A-47, Folder 145)
    - Goldsmith, Ernie (Box A-47, Folder 146)
    - Goldsmith, Geraldine (Box A-47, Folder 147)
    - Goldsmith, William H. Jr. (Box A-47, Folder 148)
    - Goldson, Philip (Box A-47, Folder 149)
      Photographer if identified: Fotografia Guerra
    - Goldstein, Clifford H. (Box A-47, Folder 150)
      Photographer if identified: FDNY/Fr. J. Biondi
    - Goldstein, Rubinette (Box A-47, Folder 151)
    - Goldwater, Barry M. (Box A-47, Folder 152)
    - Goldwire, Gladys (Box A-47, Folder 153)
    - Gole, Vincent (Box A-47, Folder 154)
    - Golphin, Joseph T. (Box A-47, Folder 155)
      Print has press release stapled to verso.
    - Golson, Benny (Box A-47, Folder 156)
    - Golson, Bobbie (Box A-47, Folder 157)
    - Golson, James (Box A-47, Folder 158)
    - Gomes, Laneda R. (Box A-47, Folder 159)
      Photographer if identified: Thomas H. Gray
    - Gonder, Jesse (Box A-47, Folder 160)
    - Gone Are The Days (Box A-47, Folder 161)
    - Gonsalves, Ivan (Box A-47, Folder 162)
      Photographer if identified: Steven Fink
    - Angelica Gonzalez (Box A-47, Folder 163)
      Print staples to ms. leaf.
    - Gonzalez, Anthony F. (Box A-47, Folder 164)
      Campaign flier.
    - Efrain Gonzalez (Box A-47, Folder 165)
    - Carter, Freddie/Thorpe, Jim (Box A-47, Folder 166)
    - Gonzales, Ramona (Box A-47, Folder 167)
    - Gonzalez, Terri (Box A-47, Folder 168)
    - Good, Mattie (Box A-47, Folder 169)
    - Good Times (Box A-47, Folder 170)
      Also 2 velox prints. 3 prints are stuck together with paste.
    - Goodall, Brenda (Box A-47, Folder 171)
    - Goode, Edith (Box A-47, Folder 172)
    - Goode, Emma Mrs. (Box A-47, Folder 173)
    - Goode, James E. Rev. (Box A-47, Folder 174)
      Photographer if identified: Dave Greene, Randolph R. Waterman,
    - Goode, Jonathan (Box A-47, Folder 175)
    - Goode, Joseph Jr. (Box A-47, Folder 176)
    - Goode, Joseph F. (Box A-47, Folder 177)
    - Goode, Katherine (Box A-47, Folder 178)
    - Goode, Mal (Box A-47, Folder 179)
      Photographer if identified: News Voice International, Monroe S. Frederick II, Office of Communication, United Church of Christ, Harris Photo,
    - Goode, Malvin R. Dr. (Box A-47, Folder 180)
    - Goode, Mattie L. Mrs. (Box A-47, Folder 181)
    - Goode, Mel (Box A-47, Folder 182)
    - Goode, Wilson (Box A-47, Folder 183)
      Also 2 newsprint photos, one mounted on cardboard. One halftone print.
      Photographer if identified: Juanita M. Cole, Pictorial Enterprise, Rick McMullin, Allied Pix Service
    - Goodell, Charles E. (Senator) (Box A-47, Folder 184)
      Photographer if identified: George DeVincent, Harris Photo, Tex Harris
    - Gooden, Ted (Box A-47, Folder 185)
    - Gooden, Terri & Gladstone (Box A-47, Folder 186)
    - Goodie, John (Box A-47, Folder 187)
      Also essay by Gordon Hancock.
    - Goodie Products (Box A-47, Folder 188)
      Photographer if identified: Ken Arnold
    - Goodie, Helen (Box A-47, Folder 189)
    - Gooding, Cuba (Box A-47, Folder 190)
      1 print is in greeting card.
      Photographer if identified: Photo by Alvin
    - Gooding, Cuba Jr. (Box A-47, Folder 191)
    - Gooding, Nancy Mrs. (Box A-47, Folder 192)
    - Gooding, Vivian (Box A-47, Folder 193)
    - Goodle, Richard (Box A-47, Folder 194)
    - Goodlett, Carlton B. Dr. (Box A-47, Folder 195)
      Also one velox print, 2 halftone prints. 2 prints have a press release stapled to verso.
      Photographer if identified: Bruce Talamon,
    - Goodley, Howard (Box A-47, Folder 196)
      Photographer if identified: James Kirk
    - Goodley, Mary E. (Box A-47, Folder 197)
    - Goodloe, Roland (Box A-47, Folder 198)
    - Goodman, Al (Box A-47, Folder 199)
    - Goodman, Benny (Box A-47, Folder 200)
      Photographer if identified: Michael Wilderman,
    - Goodman, Bernard (Box A-47, Folder 201)
    - Goodman, Curtis L. (Box A-47, Folder 202)
    - Goodman, Ernest E. (Box A-47, Folder 203)
    - Goodman, George (Box A-47, Folder 204)
    - Goodman, George W. (Box A-47, Folder 205)
    - Goodman, Robert Fet. Lt. (Box A-47, Folder 206)
      Also 1 newsprint photo.
    - Goodman, Robert L. (Box A-47, Folder 207)
    - Goodman, Sharon (Box A-47, Folder 208)
    - Goodrich, Solomon (Box A-47, Folder 209)
    - Goods, Samuel (Box A-47, Folder 210)
    - Goodson, Bee Joy (Box A-47, Folder 211)
    - Goodson, Roger (Box A-47, Folder 212)
      Also one velox print. Also one press release.
    - Goodson, Roosevelt (Box A-47, Folder 213)
    - Goodskates (Box A-47, Folder 214)
    - Goodwill Ambassador (Box A-47, Folder 215)
    - King Goodwill (Zulu King) (Box A-47, Folder 216)
    - Goodwin, Curtis (Box A-47, Folder 217)
    - Goodwin, Effie (Box A-47, Folder 218)
    - Goodwin, Mr. & Mrs. Frank (Box A-47, Folder 219)
      Photographer if identified: Dalman James, James Gilbert
    - Goodwin, Joan Maxine (Box A-47, Folder 220)
    - Goodwin, Norma Jean Dr. (Box A-47, Folder 221)
      Photographer if identified: Bradford Bachrach, United Hospital Fund,
    - Goodwin, Robert (Box A-47, Folder 222)
    - Robert Goodwin (Box A-47, Folder 223)
    - Goodwin, Wally (Box A-47, Folder 224)
    - Goodwin, William J. (Box A-47, Folder 225)
      Prints stapled together, with ms. leaf.
    - Goodwyn, Thomas Fr. (Box A-47, Folder 226)
    - Goolsby, Charles M. (Dr.) (Box A-47, Folder 227)
      Photographer if identified: Jet Commercial Photographers
    - Goolsby, Flem (Box A-47, Folder 228)
      Photographer if identified: Eli Lilly
    - Goolsby, Juliette (Box A-47, Folder 229)
    - Gopalananda, Swami (Box A-47, Folder 230)
    - Annette Gordon (Box A-47, Folder 231)
    - Gordon, Arthur Mr. & Mrs. (Box A-47, Folder 232)
    - Gordon, Barbara (Box A-47, Folder 233)
      Photographer if identified: Steve Sbarge
    - Bennie Gordon & The Soul Brothers (Box A-47, Folder 234)
      2 prints have staples through edge. 2 prints stapled together. 1 print has newspaper clipping taped to verso.
    - Gordon, Bertha (Box A-47, Folder 235)
      Photographer if identified: Board Of Education NY
    - Gordon, Portia Beverly Dr. (Box A-47, Folder 236)
    - Gordon, Bob (Box A-47, Folder 237)
      Photographer if identified: NPI Photo
    - Gordon, Diana (Box A-47, Folder 238)
    - Gordon, Dorothy (Box A-47, Folder 239)
      Photographer if identified: News Voice International, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Al Burley, Hairston, Harry J. Austin, Diane Adams, Ed Bagwell
    - Gordon, Mr. & Mrs. E. Harrison (Box A-47, Folder 240)
    - Gordon, Edmund (Box A-47, Folder 241)
      Photographer if identified: Herbert S. Sonnenfeld, Fabian Bachrach
    - Gordon, Edna (Box A-47, Folder 242)
    - Gordon Family (Box A-47, Folder 243)
    - Gordon, Harold (Box A-47, Folder 244)
    - Gordon, Honi (Box A-47, Folder 245)
      Photographer if identified: Don Schlitten
    - Gordon, Ida (Box A-47, Folder 246)
    - Gordon, Ken (Box A-47, Folder 247)
    - Gordon, Leroy (Box A-47, Folder 248)
    - Gordon, Lucky (Box A-47, Folder 249)
    - Gordon, Martha (Box A-47, Folder 250)
    - Gordon, Marva J. (Box A-47, Folder 251)
    - Gordon, Mary (Box A-47, Folder 252)
    - Michael Gordon (Box A-47, Folder 253)
      Photographer if identified: Thalhimers Photoreflex
    - Gordon, Monica Lynn (Princess) (Box A-47, Folder 254)
    - Gordon, Nettie (Box A-47, Folder 255)
    - Gordon, Phil (Box A-47, Folder 256)
      Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Gilbert Pictorial Enterprise, Irving Fitzig, Jan Jachniewicz
    - Gordon, Philip (Box A-47, Folder 257)
      Photographer if identified: William R. Devine
    - Gordon, Dexter (Box A-48, Folder 1)
    - Gordon, Portia (Box A-48, Folder 2)
    - Gordon, Quinland R. (Rev.) (Box A-48, Folder 3)
    - Gordon, Richard (Box A-48, Folder 4)
      With one typescript leaf attached by paperclip.
    - Gordon, Russell (Box A-48, Folder 5)
    - Gordon, Ruth (Box A-48, Folder 6)
      Photographer if identified: Conrad Gordon
    - Gordon, Stella L. (Box A-48, Folder 7)
    - Gordon, Susan (Box A-48, Folder 8)
    - Gordon, Von Jones (Box A-48, Folder 9)
      Photographer if identified: N.Y. Daily News
    - Gordon, Violet (Mrs.) (Box A-48, Folder 10)
    - Gordon, William (Box A-48, Folder 11)
      One print has one carbonscript leaf affixed with a staple through the border and a second staple through the border. Also two carbonscript leaves attached by staple.
    - Gordon, William H. (Box A-48, Folder 12)
    - Gordone, Charles (Box A-48, Folder 13)
      Photographer if identified: Benedict J. Fernandez, Friedman-Abeles
    - Gordy, Berry (Box A-48, Folder 14)
      Photographer if identified: Alex Berliner
    - Gordy, Berry, Jr. (Box A-48, Folder 15)
      One print has two typescript leaves attached by paperclip. Also one velox print.
    - Gordy, Berry, Sr (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-48, Folder 16)
      Photographer if identified: Pierre Bass
    - Gordy, Bert (Box A-48, Folder 17)
    - Gordy, Hazel (Box A-48, Folder 18)
    - Gordy, Robert L. (Box A-48, Folder 19)
    - Gore, Al (Box A-48, Folder 20)
    - Gore, Al (Box A-48, Folder 21)
    - Gore, Altovise (Box A-48, Folder 22)
    - Gore, Art (Box A-48, Folder 23)
    - Gore, Barbara (Box A-48, Folder 24)
    - Gore, Bertha (Box A-48, Folder 25)
    - Gore, Marilyn (Box A-48, Folder 26)
    - Gore, Robert (Mr. & Mrs.) (Box A-48, Folder 27)
      Photographer if identified: George West Photo
    - Gore, Robert B. (Box A-48, Folder 28)
      One print is a Polaroid.
      Photographer if identified: Banner Photographers, Moclovia Photographers
    - Gore, Robert L., Jr. (Box A-48, Folder 29)
    - Goree Island Memorial Service (Box A-48, Folder 30)
      Photographer if identified: K. Williams
    - Goreen, Rosalind (Box A-48, Folder 31)
      Photographer if identified: Bob Head
    - Gorham, Thelma (Box A-48, Folder 32)
    - Goring, Livingstone (Box A-48, Folder 33)
    - Goring, Rufus (Box A-48, Folder 34)
    - Goring, Ruth (Box A-48, Folder 35)
      Photographer if identified: King Photography
    - Gorman, Lillian B. (Box A-48, Folder 36)
    - Goslee, Leonard T. (Box A-48, Folder 37)
    - Gospel Cousins, The (Box A-48, Folder 38)
    - Gospel Jazz Singers (Box A-48, Folder 39)
    - Gospel Kings, The (Box A-48, Folder 40)
      Top two inches of print is torn off and reattached by paperclip.
    - Gospel Starlets (Box A-48, Folder 41)
    - Gospelaires (Box A-48, Folder 42)
      Also one velox print with caption strips stuck to the recto and verso.
    - Goss, Thomas A. (Box A-48, Folder 43)
    - Goss, Tom (Box A-48, Folder 44)
      Also three typescript leaves attached by staple.
    - Gossett, Louis (Box A-48, Folder 45)
      Also two velox prints. Two prints are attached with a paperclip to one typescript leaf. One print is attached to three typescript leaves by paperclip. One print torn across the top.
      Photographer if identified: Larry Brazil, Bert Andrews Photography, Janet Ward, Ariel Lovett
    - Gossett, Louis, Jr. (Box A-48, Folder 46)
      Photographer if identified: Oliver Upton, United Press International Photo
    - Gossett, Louis, Jr. (Box A-48, Folder 47)
    - Gossin, Lorraine (Box A-48, Folder 48)
      Also two velox prints. One velox has a newspaper clipping stuck to the verso. The other velox print has an ms. note stuck to the verso.
      Photographer if identified: James J. Kriegsmann NY, James Gilbert,
    - Gossin, Lorraine (Box A-48, Folder 49)
      Also one velox print with a ms. note stuck to the verso.
      Photographer if identified: James J. Kriegsmann NY
    - Gotbaum, Victor (Box A-48, Folder 50)
    - Gothamettes (Box A-48, Folder 51)
    - Gothard, Barbara (Box A-48, Folder 52)
    - Goudy, William (Box A-48, Folder 53)
    - Gould, Allen E., Jr. (Box A-48, Folder 54)
    - Gould, Ed (Box A-48, Folder 55)
    - Gould, Karla (Box A-48, Folder 56)
    - Gouraige, Herve (Box A-48, Folder 57)
    - Gouraige, Louretta (Box A-48, Folder 58)
    - Gourdine, Samuel (Box A-48, Folder 59)
    - Gourdine, Simon P. (Box A-48, Folder 60)
    - Gouveias, Clem (Box A-48, Folder 61)
    - Gouvinda (Box A-48, Folder 62)
    - GoVan, Barbara (Box A-48, Folder 63)
      Photographer if identified: Lichtman
    - Goran, Brenda (Box A-48, Folder 64)
    - Govan, Nurjhan B. (Box A-48, Folder 65)
    - Gowan, Chris (Box A-48, Folder 66)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Royal Photo Studio
    - Gowan, Georgia (Box A-48, Folder 67)
    - Gowdy, William R. (Box A-48, Folder 68)
    - Gowdy, William R. (Box A-48, Folder 69)
    - Gowie, Dennis (Box A-48, Folder 70)
    - Gowon, Yakubu (Box A-48, Folder 71)
      Also one velox print and one image clipped from an unidentified magazine.
    - G. Q. (Box A-48, Folder 72)
    - Grace, Bill (Box A-48, Folder 73)
    - Grace, Daddy (Box A-48, Folder 74)
      Photographer if identified: Scott L. Henderson, Robert W. Cottrol
    - Grace, Fredi & Rhinestone (Box A-48, Folder 75)
    - Grace, Patricia J. (Box A-48, Folder 76)
      Photographer if identified: Capitol and Glogau Photographers
    - Grace, Toki Lee (Box A-48, Folder 77)
      Photographer if identified: Bradforf Bachrach
    - Grace, W. Mark (Box A-48, Folder 78)
    - Grace, Wilbert (Box A-48, Folder 79)
    - Grace, Winston (Box A-48, Folder 80)
    - Gracia, G. (Box A-48, Folder 81)
    - Gracie Mansion (Box A-48, Folder 82)
    - Graddick, Richard (Box A-48, Folder 83)
      Photographer if identified: C. E. Lake
    - Graduates (Box A-48, Folder 84)
      Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, David Greene, Sherlock Robinson
    - Graduates (Box A-48, Folder 85)
      Also one negative attached to a photocopy by staple and to seven prints by paperclip. One print is a Polaroid. One print has two staples in the top left corner.
      Photographer if identified: Al Burley, Harriet Hovet, Hansen Photography, William Ballinger, Gene Luttenberg
    - Graduates 1975 (Box A-48, Folder 86)
      Two prints have staples in the corners. One print is torn. Three prints attached together by paperclip. Two prints are Polaroids.
      Photographer if identified: Joe Vericker, Guy Gillette
    - Graduates 1975 (Box A-48, Folder 87)
      One print is torn with a staple in border. Three prints are Polaroids. One print is affixed to a cardboard backing with glue.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Gill Photographers,
    - Graduates 1975 (Box A-48, Folder 88)
      Also one image clipped from a yearbook, one full leaf from a yearbook, and three images clipped from contact sheets. One print is cut out and affixed to a strip of paper backing with glue. Two prints are Polaroids. One print is affixed to one typescript leaf with tape.
      Photographer if identified: Murray Studio, Harris Photo
    - Graduates 1975 (Box A-48, Folder 89)
      Also 22 velox prints, of which four have captions affixed to the recto with glue; twelve have ms. labels stuck to the verso; one has a caption stuck to the verso with glue.
    - Graduates 1976 (Box A-48, Folder 90)
      Also three velox prints, two of which are affixed to paper backings by tape, one of which has a ms. label stuck to the verso. One print is a Polaroid. One print is affixed to two leaves by staple.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Harry J. Austin, Irving Phillips
    - Graduates 1977 (Box A-48, Folder 91)
      Three prints are stuck together.
    - Graduates 1978 (Box A-48, Folder 92)
      One print has a staple in the border. Four prints are separately attached to typescript leaves by paperclips. Two prints are affixed to paper backing by glue and attached to typescript leaf by paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Frumkin Studios
    - Graduates 1985 (Box A-48, Folder 93)
    - Grady, Berry, Jr. (Box A-48, Folder 94)
      Print is attached by paperclip to a typescript leaf.
    - Grady, Deborah (Box A-48, Folder 95)
      Photographer if identified: Allen Morgan Star Photos
    - Grady, Glenn G. (Box A-48, Folder 96)
    - Grady, Nathaniel (Rev.) (Box A-48, Folder 97)
      Print is attached by paperclip to two typescript leaves.
      Photographer if identified: Dev O'Neill
    - Grady, Pearl (Box A-48, Folder 98)
      Photographer if identified: Mark Sherman
    - Gragg, Rosa L. (Box A-48, Folder 99)
    - Graham, Billy (Rev.) (Box A-48, Folder 100)
    - Graham, Billy (Box A-48, Folder 101)
      Photographer if identified: Bert Andrews Photo
    - Graham, Billy (Box A-48, Folder 102)
      Print is a SAG membership card.
    - Graham Central Station (Box A-48, Folder 103)
      Also three velox prints, of which two have captions affixed to the recto with glue.
    - Graham, Charlotte (Box A-48, Folder 104)
    - Graham, Debra E. (Box A-48, Folder 105)
    - Graham, Edward (Box A-48, Folder 106)
    - Graham, Elaine (Box A-48, Folder 107)
      Print has ms. caption on verso.
    - Graham, Elijah J. (Box A-48, Folder 108)
    - Graham, Elizabeth (Box A-48, Folder 109)
    - Graham, Franklin D. (Box A-48, Folder 110)
      Photographer if identified: J. Peltz
    - Graham, Gladys (Dr.) (Box A-48, Folder 111)
    - Graham, Gladys (Miss) (Box A-48, Folder 112)
    - Graham, Glenn (Box A-48, Folder 113)
    - Graham, Gloria (Box A-48, Folder 114)
    - Graham, Gloria (Box A-48, Folder 115)
      Two prints attached by paperclip, one of which is folded.
    - Graham, Harry P. (Dr.) (Box A-48, Folder 116)
      Also one paper stereotype matrix. One print is attached to two typescript leaves by paperclip. One print attached to cardboard backing by tape. One print is a Polaroid.
    - Graham, Henry (Box A-48, Folder 117)
    - Graham Home for Children (Box A-48, Folder 118)
      Four prints attached by paperclip.
      Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Bramson
    - Graham, Jewel (Box A-48, Folder 119)
      Photographer if identified: Pach Bros., NY
    - Graham, Joseph M. (Box A-48, Folder 120)
      Also one computer-printed image affixed to three typescript leaves by staple.
    - Graham, Joshua (Box A-48, Folder 121)
    - Graham, Larry (Box A-48, Folder 122)
      Photographer if identified: Byron D. Hall
    - Graham, Mal (Box A-48, Folder 123)
    - Graham, Mariah (Box A-48, Folder 124)
      Print is a Polaroid. Also one velox print affixed to paper backing by tape.
    - Graham, Martha (Dance Company) (Box A-48, Folder 125)
      Prints are attached by staple.
      Photographer if identified: Tom Brazil, Martha Swope
    - Graham, Martha (Troupe) (Box A-48, Folder 126)
      Print is attached to typescript leaf by paperclip.
    - Graham, Atty & Mrs. Miles J. (Box A-48, Folder 127)
    - Graham, Moses (Box A-48, Folder 128)
    - Graham, Ralph (Box A-48, Folder 129)